// trivia questions from http://www.triviacountry.com/M14-Music-Trivia.htm
var questionOne = {
  question: 'What did "Weird Al" Yankovic call his album that contained a' +
            ' parody of a song from Michael Jackson\'s album BAD?',
  answers: ['Baddest', 'Even Worse', 'Badder', 'Good'],
  correctAnswer: 'Even Worse'
};

var questionTwo = {
  question: 'What band leader was known as "the King of Swing"?',
  answers: ['Tommy Dorsey', 'Benny Goodman', 'Guy Lombardo', 'Glenn Miller'],
  correctAnswer: 'Benny Goodman'
};

var questionThree = {
  question: 'Which one of these four Australian terms can be found in the' +
            ' lyrics of the song "Waltzing Matilda" is a tree?',
  answers: ['billabong', 'coolibah', 'jumbuck', 'tucker-bag'],
  correctAnswer: 'coolibah'
};

var questionFour = {
  question: 'Which of the following musicals was based on Thornton Wilder\'s' +
            ' comedy The Matchmaker?',
  answers: ['Hello, Dolly!', 'The Music Man', 'Take Me Along',
            'The Unsinkable Molly Brown'],
  correctAnswer: 'Hello, Dolly!'
};

var questionFive = {
  question: 'What symphony\'s last movement includes a setting of Schiller\'s' +
            ' poem "Hymn to Joy"?',
  answers: ['Beethoven\'s Ninth', 'Bruckner\'s Eight', 'Mahler\'s Tenth',
            'Mozart\'s 40th'],
  correctAnswer: 'Beethoven\'s Ninth'
};

var questionSix = {
  question: 'Gloria Estefan broke her back in what kind of accident?',
  answers: ['She fell off a stage', 'She was in a helicopter crash',
            'A tour bus accident', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'A tour bus accident'
};

var questionSeven = {
  question: 'The lyrics "By the time we got to Woodstock, we were half a' +
            ' million strong" were written by whom?',
  answers: ['Judy Collins', 'David Crosby', 'Joni Mitchell',
            'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'Joni Mitchell'
};

var questionEight = {
  question: 'Raffi is known for writing and singing what?',
  answers: ['children\'s songs', 'New Age Music', 'rap music',
            'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'New Age Music'
};

var questionNine = {
  question: 'What does Tosca throw from the roof of the prison at the end of' +
            ' the opera Tosca?',
  answers: ['her handkerchief', 'her roses', 'herself', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'herself'
};

var questionTen = {
  question: 'What does Don Giovanni descend into at the end of the opera Don' +
            ' Giovanni?',
  answers: ['hell', 'insanity', 'prison', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'hell'
};

var questionEleven = {
  question: 'The sonnet that starts out "The world is charged with the ' +
            'grandeur of God" was written by whom?',
  answers: ['Gerard Manley Hopkins', 'Henry Wadsworth Longfellow',
            'Alfred, Lord Tennyson', 'Oscar Wilde'],
  correctAnswer: 'Gerard Manley Hopkins'
};

var questionTwelve = {
  question: '"A wandering minstrel " and "Titwillow" are songs contained in' +
            ' which comic opera by Gilbert and Sullivan?',
  answers: ['The Gondoliers', 'The Mikado', 'H.M.S. Pinafore',
            'The Pirates of Penzance'],
  correctAnswer: 'The Mikado'
};

var questionThirteen = {
  question: 'In music, which of the following are "accidentals"?',
  answers: ['finger cymbals and castanets', 'mistakes made while playing',
            'sharps and flats', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'sharps and flats'
};

var questionFourteen = {
  question: 'In the Opera Faust, Faust wins Marguerite\'s love with what?',
  answers: ['candy', 'jewelry', 'roses', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'jewelry'
};

var questionFifteen = {
  question: 'The piano piece known as "The Minute Waltz" was written by whom?',
  answers: ['Johannes Brahms', 'Frederic Chopin', 'Franz Liszt',
            'Sergei Rachmaninoff'],
  correctAnswer: 'Frederic Chopin'
};

var questionSixteen = {
  question: 'The musical work, The Sorcerer\'s Apprentice, was written by whom?',
  answers: ['Paul Dukas', 'Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart', 'Maurice Ravel',
            'Camille Saint-Saens'],
  correctAnswer: 'Paul Dukas'
};

var questionSeventeen = {
  question: 'What song writer wrote the song with the line "Mad dogs and' +
            ' Englishmen go out in the mid-day sun" in it?',
  answers: ['Noel Coward', 'Gilbert and Sullivan', 'Cole Porter',
            'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'Noel Coward'
};

var questionEighteen = {
  question: 'Whose debut album "Forever Your Girl" sold over 5,000,000 albums?',
  answers: ['Paula Abdul', 'Sade', 'Tiffany', 'None of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'Paula Abdul'
};

var questionNineteen = {
  question: 'A song called "Party All the Time", released in 1985, reached' +
            ' the # 2 spot on Billboard\'s pop charts. Which Saturday Night' +
            ' Live actor recorded the song?',
  answers: ['Garrett Morris', 'Eddie Murphy', 'Bill Murray', 'Joe Piscopo'],
  correctAnswer: 'Eddie Murphy'
};

var questionTwenty = {
  question: 'Two of Barbara Cook\'s most popular songs, "Dear Friend" and' +
            ' Vanilla Ice Cream", were provided by what musical?',
  answers: ['Candide', 'Carousel', 'The Music Man', 'She Loves Me'],
  correctAnswer: 'She Loves Me'
};

// make an array for use later
var objects = [
  questionOne, questionTwo, questionThree, questionFour, questionFive,
  questionSix, questionSeven, questionEight, questionNine, questionTen,
  questionEleven, questionTwelve, questionThirteen, questionFourteen,
  questionFifteen, questionSixteen, questionSeventeen, questionEighteen,
  questionNineteen, questionTwenty
];
